Now, descendant of Romuald Blood, Mizumura Shinta.
I ask of you to create a new life with me to give rise to the new Strigoli.
Is this a all right, Kishimoto-san?
Wh-Wh-What should I do next?
Kishimoto-san?
What have you been waiting for?
You guys sure are slow. I was bored to death.
This guy... This will be no walk in the park.
WYD.
What are you doing?
Isn't it obvious?
I'm a bodyguard.
The time for me to become useful has arrived.
hanarenaide hanasanaide
Don't leave and don't let go
sono kodou ga tomaru made
Until this heart stops beating
Uchi nare koe wa wazawai no shirabe
My inner voice keeps repeating
mikan no akumu kurikaeshite iru
A melody of disaster, an incomplete nightmare
kono inga tachikireru nara ba
Should I manage to break this cycle of fate
ochite mo kuyamanai
I would have no regret even if it means my doom
utsuro na hai ni bishu wo mitashitara
When the empty cup fills with the finest wine
A sacrifice will be made at the altar
saidan no ue sasageru wa kumotsu
While I yearn for salvation
kyuusai no yume kogare nagara
The hell fire burns my heart
mune yaku gouka
Come, lay a sweet kiss on me, my life stripped bare
saa mukidashi no sono inochi amaku kuchizukete
The noble sacrifice engraved in my skin
hada ni kizamu toutoi gisei
Love no one else but me
watashi dake aishite
Until the day I stop breathing
iki no taeru toki made
Embrace the the corpse weeping crimson tears.
akai namida nagashi nakigara daite ageru
This accursed fate
norowareta sadame wo
This unerasable stigma
nuguenai rakuin wo
Wash them clean with your blood
anata no chi de araikiyomete
And we'll be reborn
umarekawaru
In the darkness we dance madly between life and death
sei to shi to ga yami ni junkan suru
In this holy night
S-Sorry, I started to do something horrible.
There's no need to apologize.
What happened earlier was what I wanted.
Umm... I shouldn't say this after doing that, but...
Kishimoto-san, you should take better care of your body.
Useless.
I guess she hates me now.
Damn it, this seriously sucks.
If you're this beat—
What was that for?
And here I am being nice to you.
So she had a bodyguard?
PLM.
Put your life on the line for the mission.
Commander Cliff...
WSC.
We must be both smooth and smart when conducting our next operation.
We won't fail next time.
We will need reinforcements.
Weapons are all we need.
He has a tongue!
That's right...
In the tragedy of Sarashu, a certain wife gave us one hard time.
Come, I'll take you all with me.
Retreat! Retreat immediately!
Lilith, this is farewell.
Commander Cliff, are you unhurt?
Damn her. That crazy woman took out Captain Odin Romuald.
Father. Mother.
Hey, where's Mom?
Lilith, your mother had something important to do.
Mom. I want to see Mom.
Since you're a good girl I'll give you this.
This is the only thing your parents can give you.
Here we go.
Thanks to my parents protecting me, I'm now the sole survivor of the Sarashu incident.
That's why...
I can't die until I fulfill my mission.
Hey, look at that.
Yuck, look at how they are kissing.
They are really into it.
My boyfriend and I aren't even close to that.
Yuck, and you want to imitate them?
Let's go.
Hey, wait.
I needed that snack.
Hey, somebody has collapsed here.
This is very bad.
Away we go.
Shinta...
He was really serious.
Those eyes...
Those eyes were lusting over my body.
Shinta's a guy after all.
And all guys are after that sort of thing.
I... I...
K-Kamiura?
Woah, awesome.
You were able to tell.
I'm so happy.
What are you doing here?
How did you get in?
Huh? I'm your guardian.
And your guardian should always be by your side and embrace you like this.
You don't need to cling, Kamuira.
Are you shy?
I won't let go.
Stop it!
Your waist has become a perfect complement to your figure.
Did fucking your boyfriend daily help with your figure?
It must be delicious.
As a woman, I'm jealous.
You came here just to do this?
That's right.
I wanted to see if this nice body could live up to the task.
Hey, hey. Is he rough with you?
What's with that?
Lighten up, will you?
She surely hates me.
Hey, hey, Lilith. Listen, listen!
A bunch of guys tried to intrude but I beat them up by myself.
I'm amazing, right?
Praise me, Lilith.
Praise me, prai—
What are you doing down there?
You're as ugly as ever.
Kamiura?
What are you doing here and when did you get in?
Wait, what was I saying?
Aren't you supposed to be Lilith's bodyguard?
Falling asleep on the bed like that.
Get a grip already, ugly.
I'm doing a very good job protecting her!
Bye, Ugly.
Eh?
What's up her butt?
We've gone so long without seeing each other and that's the first thing she does?
There you are, Plum.
Don't...
I know.
My inescapable destiny.
That mark on your chest is proof of your oath with the Moroi.
Your mission is to give birth to the child of Romuald blood,
then kill both father and child, and bathe in their blood.
A righteous act, all for the sake of the Strigoli.
If you can't complete it, that mark will become your curse for all eternity.
Kamiura, it's not that I'm scared of losing my virginity.
No matter what happens, I will show you that I can have his child.
My determination will not falter.
I feel better after hearing those words.
Kishimoto-san...
What's this even when sitting next to me?
This behavior is unforgivable.
She's been looking at me since class started.
She doesn't hate me.
I'm glad.
Shin-chan, we both came from Kyushu.
Can't you see? You can't beat a childhood friend.
There is no way I will lose to that new student.
You hear that, Shin-chan?
Ouch.
It's bleeding.
Jeez.
I wonder if it's deep...
Huh?
The wound disappeared?
TBF.
What's that?
This refreshing breeze gives a calming feel.
I don't understand.
Is that so?
So, what should we do about him?
Are we seriously going to force him to awaken?
Commander Cliff Strife.
He is the descendant of the Romuald bloodline.
It would be good if we could do that.
I don't mind.
We need him to deal with the Strigoli.
It would be good if he agreed to help.
Especially in dealing with the Moroin.
I don't know if the people of this world can handle
all this strangeness.
Basically,
SMH,
right?
What's that, Cammot?
Ah, you can't play with that.
I got this from Grandma.
It's a memento of my mother.
It feels like there's a rock in here.
What's this thing?
Has this always been in there?
My chest...
it hurts...
Oh, Shinta's starting to awaken.
C-Cammot?
You've awoken.
It was said that you would.
Wha—C-Cammot?
You are Cammot, right?
Shinta, a lot of scary stuff is about to start.
You better be careful.
But...
It's all good!
Cammot is here with you!
I couldn't land properly.
Oh, Shinta. Does your chest still hurt?
It's fine.
Anyway, who are you?
I'm Cammot.
Cammo—
It's all good!
Aren't you a cat?
Cammot is on your side.
But why is a cat talk—
It's all good!
As long as I'm here you will be all good!
Oh yeah, Shinta...
Be careful around that red-eyed, red-haired girl.
Huh, red?
Shinta's
Hopeless Diary
Read these.
What are these?
Hopeless Shinta Diary?
This one is...
Shinta's
Hopeless Diary
Shinta's first perverted day.
And this one is when Shinta freaked out when baby fur grew under his privates.
Wait a minute! I didn't freak out when baby fur—
Eh? Baby fur?
It's all good!
I've always been by your side so ask me anything.
That's not what I meant...
So you really wrote these, Cammot?
What happened when my mother died is here.
And even when Grandpa died.
Eh, Romuald?
Where have I heard that word before?
...Romuald bloodline.
Kishimoto-san...
Those are the same words she said.
Kishimoto-san, just what are you after?
Romuald bloodline.
I've heard that before.
Grandpa used to say those words.
It's no use. I can't remember.
What's that?
Wh-What?
S-Sakamoto?
Romuald bloodline.
Love between a Strigoli and a hunter won't be tolerated.
Because your blood will get in the way.
"My blood will get in the way"?
Hey, Sakamoto.
Huh, Shin-chan?
What are you doing in a place like this?
Let's go eat lunch.
Sorry, but not today.
Why not!?
Are you not feeling well?
I just need some time alone to think some things through.
Sorry.
Wait, Shin-chan.
I needed to talk to you about something.
My body is acting a bit strange.
I cut my finger and the bleeding stopped immediately.
No matter how much it hurts, the wound disappears so fast.
It's almost as if I'm not human anymore.
It's weird, isn't it?
Help me, Shin-chan.
I'm scared.
Silver bullets...
It won't be long until all of them have been blessed.
Headquarters have given us a lot of stuff with that letter.
TCM.
That just shows they want us to complete this mission by sending them.
When the Romuald descendant awakens,
they want us to have an advantage in case things go wrong.
Once the descendant awakens
he will probably kill the target.
DKT.
My favorite food.
Even better, it's in honey.
Tonight is going to be good.
Silver chains...
Lilith, be careful.
Did I wake you?
Sorry, but mind if I borrow that face of yours?
Lilith, sorry.
These silver chains render my powers useless.
Yes, who is it?
This is...
A message from Cliff-sensei.
Such a nice view.
A long time ago,
rather naughty people were embarrassed publicly
by the command of the governor to dunk them in water.
As a spectator, I'm enjoying the same scene.
I don't know if you've noticed,
but these guns are loaded with silver bullets.
If I shot you with one of these you would be destroyed,
which would prove that you are not human.
You don't want to end the Strigoli, do you?
Start begging for your life.
Come on!
This is good.
This gun is capable of killing you no matter how much you beg.
Watch it.
Don't talk or it might go off.
Like this...
Sorry to disappoint you,
but it's not my duty to pull the trigger.
The one who will should be here soon.
Until then, behave.
P-Pervert,
is toying with people's lives one of your hobbies?
I'm not done yet.
Cold, white skin.
What are you doing?
Look at this,
whenever I apply pressure the nipple stands out.
You're not that bad with a body like this.
I thought the Strigoli's white cold flesh would be hard to cut.
Stop it!
What should I do next?
Should I play with your belly button?
Or maybe you could grasp it with your teeth.
I wonder if you will still be cold?
Probably not.
Your body's cold from the start, and it won't change.
S-Stop it.
What are you going to do?
Isn't it obvious?
Have you heard of the word casso  before?
It means "to cause destruction" in Latin.
A fitting term for the Strigoli and Moroi.
Okasu is a similar word in Japanese which means to rape.
You'll be destroyed anyway.
What about that?
Is my spit a form of casso?
It's a word made up by those like yourself who didn't want to die.
It's a repetition of god's words.
It means to clean up the garbage, basically.
I don't care what you do!
Even if you try to break me by defiling my body, I will never—
Wh-What are you doing here?
Kishimoto-san?
Why?
We have been awaiting your arrival, Romuald descendant.
Eh? Cliff-sensei.
What are you doing in this place?
Hurry! Help her right now!
Don't call the name of that garbage.
What kind of joke is this?
That girl isn't human.
You're worrying about a bug.
Bug?
It's your duty to eliminate such a being.
Please use this sword.
Go on.
"Eliminate"?
What are you saying? I can't...
LKO.
You shall learn how we keep social order in this world.
What is this LK you are talking about?
All of this—
Don't worry.
I'll help you with this.
So, descendant.
Lets do this together.
Please wait.
If Kishimotos-san gets hit she'll die.
Of course she will die.
What are you saying?
Let me teach you how adults do things.
No, this is different from normal adults, sensei.
Let me go.
Please let me go, Sensei.
I'm begging you.
It's all right. She isn't human.
This silver sword can conveniently kill her in one hit and leave no trace.
No, Cliff-sensei. I'm begging you.
Please stop. We shouldn't be doing this.
I don't want to kill someone!
Yes, we must.
For the future.
He's awoken.
How dare you!
Stop it. He's the descendant.
Let's leave for now.
But then...
It's just as the legend says...
RQP.
Retreat as quickly as possible.
Roger.
This means you've become an adult, descendant.
This is all for tonight.
I'll see you later.
Good bye.
Sorry, I'm not looking.
It's all right now.
Kishimoto-san,
it's good you're okay.
Thanks.
My days just keep on repeating
nandomo kurakaesu my days
An echo that makes my head hurt
atama wo yusaburu zankyou
Ah, these fragile feelings I've been hiding
aa kowaresou da boku no kakushita ura no kanjou
That you will reveal in the future
mirai ni dare ga furerareru no
Come on, just a little bit
sukoshi kurai wa ii jan ka
Nobody understands, nobody knows
dare ni mo wakaranai nobody knows
And yet
soredemo
Your delicate feelings
kimi no sensai na omoi ga
And sharp anxiety
eiri na fuan wa mou
Are starting to pierce through me
boku ni tsukisashite
The feelings we screamed out are so far away
futari no koe sakenda omoi wa zutto tooku
I know we'll manage to overcome fate
unmei mo kitto koerareru darou
So that the reality we painted doesn't smear
irozuita ima nijimanai you ni
Bite those lips and don't let go
sono kuchibiru ni ha wo tatete hanasanai